Mss.B.In6
American Philosophical Society
- Series V. Printed Materials
  - Amateur's Aquarium Club, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1945 March 14; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The American Printer, Vol. 82, No. 6, 1926 March 20; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The American Printer, Vol. 80, No. 4, 1929 February 20; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. III, No. 36, 1895 July; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No.1, 1912 April; 2.0 items (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 2, 1912 May; 2.0 items (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 3, 1912 June; 2.0 items (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 4, 1912 September; 2.0 items (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 5, 1912 October; 2.0 items (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 6, 1912 November; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 7, 1912 December; 2.0 items (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 8, 1913 January; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 9, 1913 February; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. I, No. 10, 1913 March; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 1, 1913 April; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 2, 1913 May; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 3, 1913 June; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 4, 1913 September; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 5, 1913 October; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 6, 1913 November; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. II, No. 7, 1913 December; 3.0 items (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. IV, No. 5, 1935 September; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Aquarium, Vol. XXIII, No. 2, 1954 February; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The Aquarium (subscription forms), undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Aquarium Fish: Series 2, undated; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Aquarium Society of Philadelphia (membership card), 1907 January; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Het Aquarium, No. 1, 1948 June; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Het Aquarium, No. 3, 1948 August; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Het Aquarium, No. 12, 1957 May; 1.0 item (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - The Benjamin Franklin Gazette, 1928 October; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Benjamin Franklin Gazette, 1929 January; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - The Benjamin Franklin Gazette, 1929 October; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Benjamin Franklin Gazette, 1930 May; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Benjamin Franklin Gazette, 1931 May; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Benjamin Franklin Gazette, 1931 November; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "The Book of Designations: The Benjamin Franklin Memorial and the Franklin Institute Museum", undated; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "The Colorado Aquarist", 1949 April; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Coming Events in Britain", 1960 April; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Complete Photographer, Issue No. 4, Volume No. 1, 1941 October; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Copeia, 1943 October 15; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Finlay Natural-Color Photography Process, undated; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The Fish Culturist, 1945 March - 1948 September; 3.0 items (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The First Printers and Their Books, 1940; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "Goldfish: Their Care in Small Aquaria and Ponds", 1931 October; 2.0 items (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "Graphic Arts Education: Proceedings of the Conference Dinner", 1947 January; 2.0 items (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "Graphic Arts Frolic Modernistic Nite", 1929 April 4; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The Graphic Arts Monthly, 1930 April; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Ichthys: Peces y Acuarios, 1952 December; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - The Inland Printer, Vol. 79, No. 1, 1927 April; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - The Inland Printer, Vol. 79, No. 3, 1927 June; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - The Inland Printer, Vol. 79, No. 4, 1927 July; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - The Inland Printer, Vol. 80, No. 2, 1927 November; 1.0 item (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - The Keystone Printer, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1922 December; 4.0 items (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Keystone Printer, Vol. 1, No. 4, 1923 March; 1.0 item (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Keystone Printer, Vol. 1, No. 10, 1923 October; 1.0 item (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Keystone Printer, Vol. 2, No. 9, 1924 October; 1.0 item (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Maps, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Maps
    Several maps and letters discussing rivers.
  - Miscellaneous Materials, No. 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, No. 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, No. 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, No. 4 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, No. 5, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Miscellaneous Materials, No. 5
    Miscellaneous material. Includes copies of Mrs. William T. Innes' obituary.
  - Miscellaneous Materials, No. 6, 1923 - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Folder consists of invitations to various events.
  - Missouri Botanical Garden Bulletin, 1941 March; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - National Geographic Magazine, 1924 October; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Natural History Magazine, 1961 June - July; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Nature Magazine, 1924 June; 3.0 items (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Fish Culturalists' Association, 1931-1932; 3.0 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, 1949 October 2; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 6)
    A mutli-page spread in the Philadelphia Inquirer discussing the work of William T. Innes.
  - Philadelphia Market Facts: Water, 1950; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Philadelphia Market Facts
    A pamphlet distributed by the Philadelphia Inquirer concerning the hardness of water in the Philadelphia retail area.
  - Printing, Vol. 40, No. 6, 1927 May 7; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Printing, Vol. 41, No. 10, 1927 September 3; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Printing, Vol. 41, No. 12, 1927 September 17; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Printing, Vol. 42, No. 6, 1927 November 5; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Taschenkalender fur Aquarienfreunde, 1921; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Temple University and the Tide: Presidents Report", 1959 - 1960; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Temple University Alumni Review, 1961 January; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Typo Topics, Vol. IV, No. 4-5, 1946 June - July; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Typothetae Bulletin, Vol. 22, No. 24, 1926 March 15; 2.0 items (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Typothetae Bulletin, Vol. 34, No. 4, 1931 November 15; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Westvaco: Inspirations for Printers, No. 82, 1933; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Westvaco: Inspirations for Printers, No. 86, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Westvaco: Inspirations for Printers, No. 87, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Westvaco: Inspirations for Printers, No. 88, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Wochenschrift: fur Aquarien - u. Terrarienkunde, 1950 December; 1.0 item (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Series VI. Graphic Materials
  - Aquarium Photographs (Misc.) No. 1, undated; 20.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Aquarium Photographs (Misc.) No. 1
    Miscellaneous photographs of various aquariums.
  - Aquarium Photographs (Misc.) No. 2, undated; 10.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Aquarium Photographs (Misc.) No. 3, undated; 25.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Aquarium Photographs (Misc.) No. 3
    Miscellaneous photographs of various aquariums including John G. Shed, New York, and Steinhart Aquariums.
  - Aquatic Plant Photographs (mounted) No. 1, undated; 5.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Aquatic Plant Photographs (mounted) No. 2, undated; 10.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Aquatic Plant Photographs (mounted) No. 3, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Aquatic Plant Photographs (unmounted) No. 1, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Aquatic Plant Photographs (unmounted) No. 2, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 5-40 (not inclusive), 1951; 18.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 41-71 (not inclusive), 1951; 17.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 73 - 89 (not inclusive), 12.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 91-96 (not inclusive), 10.0 Photograph(s) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 97-107 (not inclusive), 1951; 13.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 116-142 (not inclusive), 1951; 17.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 144-152 (not inclusive), 1951; 10.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 154-160., 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 162-168 (not inclusive), 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 170-176., 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 177-181., 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 182-187., 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 188-195 (not inclusive), 1951; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 204-210 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 212-217., 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 219-228 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 229-239 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 240-248 (not inclusive), 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 249-257 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 258-265 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 266-273., 1951; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 274-282 (not inclusive), 1951; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 284-299 (not inclusive), 1951; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 300-308 (not inclusive), 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 309-325 (not inclusive), 1951; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 328-336 (not inclusive), 1951; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 337-344 (not inclusive), 1951; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 346-365 (not inclusive), 1951; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 366-377 (not inclusive), 1951; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 385-398 (not inclusive), 1951; 10.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 402-413 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 418-426 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 426-431, 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 433-443 (not inclusive), 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 444-456 (not inclusive), 1951; 11.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 457-461, 1951; 5.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 464-472 (not inclusive), 1951; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 473-481 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 482-494 (not inclusive), 1951; 11.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Exotic Aquarium Fishes, 12th ed." Photo proofs, pp. 496-514 (not inclusive), 1951; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Fish Cards: A, No. 1, undated; 7.0 items (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fish Cards: A, No. 2, undated; 6.0 items (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Fish Cards: A, No. 3, undated; 8.0 items (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Fish Cards: A, No. 4, undated; 7.0 items (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Fish Cards: A, No. 5, undated; 7.0 items (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Fish Cards: B, No. 1, undated; 12.0 items (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Fish Cards: B, No. 2, undated; 8.0 items (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Fish Cards: B, No. 3, undated; 12.0 items (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Fish Cards: C, No. 1, undated; 10.0 items (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fish Cards: C, No. 2, undated; 7.0 items (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fish Cards: C, No. 3, undated; 8.0 items (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fish Cards: C, No. 4, undated; 6.0 items (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fish Cards: C, No. 5, undated; 6.0 items (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fish Cards: C, No. 6, undated; 4.0 items (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fish Cards: D, undated; 7.0 items (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Fish Cards: E, undated; 5.0 items (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Fish Cards: F, undated; 10.0 items (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Fish Cards: G, undated; 8.0 items (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Fish Cards: H, No. 1, undated; 6.0 items (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fish Cards: H, No. 2, undated; 8.0 items (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fish Cards: H, No. 3, undated; 6.0 items (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Fish Cards: H, No. 4, undated; 4.0 items (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fish Cards: J, undated; 1.0 item (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Fish Cards: L, undated; 10.0 items (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Fish Cards: M, No. 1, undated; 5.0 items (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Fish Cards: M, No. 2, undated; 7.0 items (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Fish Cards: M, No. 3, undated; 7.0 items (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Fish Cards: N, undated; 8.0 items (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Fish Cards: O, undated; 6.0 items (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Fish Cards: P, No. 1, undated; 7.0 items (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Fish Cards: P, No. 2, undated; 9.0 items (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Fish Cards: P, No. 3, undated; 7.0 items (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Fish Cards: P, No. 4, undated; 9.0 items (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fish Cards: P, No. 5, undated; 6.0 items (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fish Cards: R, No. 1, undated; 6.0 items (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fish Cards: R, No. 2, undated; 9.0 items (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fish Cards: S, undated; 8.0 items (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fish Cards: T, No. 1, undated; 4.0 items (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fish Cards: T, No. 2, undated; 5.0 items (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fish Cards: W, undated; 2.0 items (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fish Cards: X, undated; 10.0 items (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fish Photographs, 1-20 (non-inclusive), undated; 16.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Fish Photographs, 21-58, undated; 37.0 items (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Fish Photographs, 52-95 (non-inclusive), 37.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fish Photographs, A-B, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Fish Photographs, C, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fish Photographs, D, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fish Photographs, E-F, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Fish Photographs, G, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Fish Photographs, H-J, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Fish Photographs, K-L, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fish Photographs, M, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fish Photographs, N, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fish Photographs, P-Q, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fish Photographs, R, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Fish Photographs, S-T, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fish Photographs, "Goldfish Series", undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fish Photographs, "Goldfish Varieties", 1931; 21.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 1, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 2, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 3, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 4, undated; 10.0 Photograph(s) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 5, undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 6, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 7, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 8, undated; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 9, undated; 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 10, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 11, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 12, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 13, undated; 12.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 14, undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 15, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 16, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 17, undated; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 18, undated; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 19, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 20, undated; 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 21, undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 22, undated; 11.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 23, undated; 5.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 24, undated; 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 25, undated; 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 26, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 27, undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 28, undated; 14.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 29, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 30, undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 31, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 32, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 33, undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 34, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 35, undated; 11.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 36, undated; 12.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 37, 1953; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 26
    Contains photographs used for the 1953 edition of William T. Innes' "The Aquarium."
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 38, undated; 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 27
    Both positive and negative copies of a photograph of an angelfish.
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 39, undated; 2.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 28
    Reproduction photo sequence. Note on back from William T. Innes: "I find this to be a very valuable original."
  - Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 40, undated; 7.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Fish Photographs (mounted), No. 29
    A series of photographs and one sketch.
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 1, undated; 32.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 1
    Reproduction photographs. Includes a drawing of a diagram.
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 2, undated; 5.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 2
    A series of five photographs.
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 3, undated; 13.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 4, undated; 71.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 5, undated; 70.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 6, undated; 35.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 7, undated; 40.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 8, undated; 30.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 9, undated; 30.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 10, undated; 20.0 Photograph(s) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted). No. 11, undated; 60.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 12, undated; 27.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 13, undated; 28.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 14, undated; 22.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 15, undated; 19.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 16, undated; 28.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 17, undated; 25.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Fish Photographs (unmounted), No. 18, undated; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 1, undated; 5.0 items (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Fish Sketches, No. 1
    Folder contains sketches of fish and aquariums.
  - Fish Sketches, No. 2, undated; 11.0 items (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 3, undated; 17.0 items (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 4, undated; 7.0 items (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 5, undated; 3.0 items (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 6, undated; 4.0 items (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 7, undated; 4.0 items (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 8, undated; 6.0 items (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 9, undated; 5.0 items (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 10, undated; 6.0 items (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 11, undated; 21.0 items (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 12, undated; 17.0 items (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 13, undated; 7.0 items (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 14, undated; 2.0 items (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Fish Sketches, No. 14
    Cover sketch for "Exotic and Aquarium Fishes."
  - Fish Sketches, No. 15, undated; 12.0 items (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 16, undated; 22.0 items (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 17, undated; 6.0 items (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 18, undated; 5.0 items (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Fish Sketches, No. 19, undated; 33.0 items (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Fish Sketches, No. 19
    Sketches drawn by Fritz Mayer.
  - Fish Slides, No. 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Fish Slides, No. 2, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Fish Slides, No. 3, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Fish Slides, No. 4, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)